https://www.franklowe.com/privacy-policy/

Call Us: (800) 777-0202
Get a Quote
You are here:
Home »Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how
we collect, use, communicate and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.When accessing the FrankLowe.com website, Frank Lowe will learn certain
information
about you during your visit.Similar to other commercial websites, our website utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation
below) and server logs to collect information about how our site is used. Information gathered through cookies and
server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our site, and the websites
visited just before and just after our own, as well as your IP address.Use of CookiesA cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a
website, that site"s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive
specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser"s
preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has
already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.IP AddressesIP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that
is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web
server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you
request) can be sent to you.Email InformationIf you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with
your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we
employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone. This also applies when you register
for our website, sign up through any of our forms using your email address or make a purchase on this site. For
further information see the email policies below.How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing
customer service and making available other items and services to our customers and prospective customers.Frank Lowe will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our
site,
unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to
unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the
law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.Email PoliciesWe are committed to keeping your e-mail address confidential. We do not sell, rent, or lease our subscription lists
to third parties, and we will not provide your personal information to any third party individual, government
agency, or company at any time unless strictly compelled to do so by law.We will use your e-mail address solely to provide timely information about Frank Lowe.We will maintain the information you send via e-mail in accordance with applicable federal law.CAN-SPAM ComplianceIn compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mail sent from our organization will clearly state who the e-mail is from
and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all e-mail messages will also contain
concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further e-mail
communication from us.Choice/Opt-OutOur site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners by reading
the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of any e-mail they receive from us at anytime.Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these
communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail.Use of External LinksFrankLowe.com may contain links to many other websites. Frank Lowe cannot
guarantee
the accuracy of information found at any linked site. Links to or from external sites not owned or controlled
by Frank Lowedo not constitute an endorsement by Frank Lowe or any of its employees of
the sponsors of these sites or the products or information presented therein.By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all
applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws.
If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials
contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.Intellectual Property RightsAll copyrights, trademarks, patents and other intellectual property rights in and on our website and all content and
software located on the site shall remain the sole property of Frank Lowe or its licensors.
The use
of our trademarks, content and intellectual property is forbidden without the express written consent
from Frank Lowe.You must not:Republish material from our website without prior written consent.Sell or rent material from our website.Reproduce, duplicate, create derivative, copy or otherwise exploit material on our website for any purpose.Redistribute any content from our website, including onto another website.Acceptable UseYou agree to use our website only for lawful purposes, and in a way that does not infringe the rights of, restrict or
inhibit anyone else"s use and enjoyment of the website. Prohibited behavior includes harassing or causing distress
or inconvenience to any other user, transmitting obscene or offensive content or disrupting the normal flow of
dialogue within our website.You must not use our website to send unsolicited commercial communications. You must not use the content on our
website for any marketing related purpose without our express written consent.Restricted AccessWe may in the future need to restrict access to parts (or all) of our website and reserve full rights to do so. If,
at any point, we provide you with a username and password for you to access restricted areas of our website, you
must ensure that both your username and password are kept confidential.Use of TestimonialsIn accordance to with the FTC guidelines concerning the use of endorsements and testimonials in advertising, please
be aware of the following:Testimonials that appear on this site are actually received via text, audio or video submission. They are individual
experiences, reflecting real life experiences of those who have used our products and/or services in some way. They
are individual results and results do vary. We do not claim that they are typical results. The testimonials are not
necessarily representative of all of those who will use our products and/or services.The testimonials displayed in any form on this site (text, audio, video or other) are reproduced verbatim, except for
correction of grammatical or typing errors. Some may have been shortened. In other words, not the whole message
received by the testimonial writer is displayed when it seems too lengthy or not the whole statement seems relevant
for the general public.Frank Lowe is not responsible for any of the opinions or comments posted
on FrankLowe.com. Frank Lowe is not a forum for testimonials, however provides testimonials as a means for
customers to share their experiences with one another. To protect against abuse, all testimonials appear after they
have been reviewed by management of Frank Lowe. Frank Lowe doe not
share the
opinions, views or commentary of any testimonials on FrankLowe.com - the opinions are strictly
the
views of the testimonial source.The testimonials are never intended to make claims that our products and/or services can be used to diagnose, treat,
cure, mitigate or prevent any disease. Any such claims, implicit or explicit, in any shape or form, have not been
clinically tested or evaluated.How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private
information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may
enter on our website may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit
Card information and other sensitive information is never transmitted via email.Frank Lowe may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such
purposes
as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least
interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all
users, Frank Loweuses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change
information, or otherwise cause damage.Disclaimer and Limitation of LiabilityFrank Lowe makes no representations, warranties, or assurances as to the accuracy, currency or
completeness of the content contain on this website or any sites linked to this site.All the materials on this site are provided "as is" without any express or implied warranty of any kind, including
warranties of merchantability, noninfringement of intellectual property or fitness for any particular purpose. In no
event shall Frank Lowe or its agents or associates be liable for any damages whatsoever
(including,
without limitation, damages for loss of profits, business interruption, loss of information, injury or death)
arising out of the use of or inability to use the materials, even if Frank Lowe has been
advised of
the possibility of such loss or damages.Policy ChangesWe reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that
if the privacy policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under
this privacy policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this privacy policy, without your prior
consent.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the
confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.ContactIf you have any questions regarding this policy, or your dealings with our website, please contact us
here: https://www.franklowe.com/contact/Frank Lowe44 Ramsey Road, Shirley, NY 11967
© 2020 Frank Lowe | Disclaimer | Web Accessibility Statement | Privacy Policy
